VICTOR WILLIAMS

Full Stack Developer

444 N 4th Street, 401 Philadelphia, PA 19123 484-895-5489 vaporjawn.github.io/

vrwilliams719@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Freelance software developer with strong analytical skills and proficiency in mathematics. Individual with ability to follow established procedures and work under little or no supervision. Bringing expertise in writing full-stack code to support multiple platforms, including web, android, and iOS, and a solid grasp of data structures and object- oriented designs.

EDUCATION

Temple University,

Philadelphia, PA May 2019

 Bachelor of Arts: Computer Science and Criminal Justice

Certificate: Computer

Security

•Studied the subjects of Discrete Mathematics, Differential Calculus, Data Structures, Algorithms, and Operating Systems within the Computer Science Curriculum.

EXPERIENCE

AmeriCorps

Information Technology Manager

Aug. 2019 - Jan. 2020

- Refined and improved the existing documentation within the system
- Web development and maintenance for various School District websites
- Managed and repaired all technology in Taggart John H. School
- Skills: Angular.JS, API, Cloud, JSON, HTML5, CSS

BitGamer

Nov. 2018 - Nov. 2019

Dec. 2016 - July 2018

Full Stack Developer / Tournament Organizer

- Developed a tournament hosting web application along with a small team
- Communicated with other companies to increase collaborative business opportunities
- Managed the social media platforms for the company's likeness
- Skills: React.js, Node.js, RESTfulAPI, AWS, Java, Python, HTML5

CrystalFruit

Full Stack Developer

- Developed full-stack web applications which processed, analyzed, and rendered data
- Maintained and updated websites upon request per client
- Planned, wrote, and debugged web applications and software with complete accuracy
- Skills: Bootstrap, Vue.js, MongoDB, Git, API, PHP, Ruby, HTML5, CSS

KEY SKILLS -

JavaScript, ReactJS, Android, JSON, Rust, HTML5, Vue, Java, Node, RESTfulAPIs, MongoDB, Git, Bootstrap, AWS, Go, Python, Unity, AngularJS, CSS, C#, SQL, and Swift

ACTIVITIES

Temple University Development Team - EBoard Computer Science Tutor, Temple University (ACM) Association for Computing Machinery PennApps at University of Pennsylvania Alliance for Minority Participation in STEM The Odyssey Online The Tab Editorial Let's Get Ready SAT Prep Program Owlchestra, Violinist